Cole Miller

Accomplished leader with 4 years of Military Service and 3 years of providing excellent customer service. Seeking opportunities where I can apply my Full Stack Developer skills into a career.

Dallas, TX (817) 733-2566 cole.t.miller@gmail.com Portfolio

EDUCATION

Southern Methodist University — Full Stack Developer

2019 - PRESENT

Full Stack Coding Program through SMU. Expecting to graduate in February of 2020.

EXPERIENCE

Costco Wholesale — *Tire Center Supervisor*

2017 - 2019

Ensure that the Tire Center is being run as efficiently as possible. Monitor technicians to make sure all vehicles are completed on time. Train new employees and motivate team to increase the number of jobs per day.

Costco Wholesale — *Tire Center Installer*

2016 - 2017

Offer customer service and assist clients with a vast knowledge of the products and services at hand. Replaced tires on customer's vehicles.

US Army — Sergeant

2013 - 2015

Managed a team through day to day activities and strenuous tasks to include a deployment to Afghanistan. Provide purpose, direction, and motivation to complete tasks on time. Conducted classes and training courses for my team. Supervise and refine day to day activities of my team to uphold Army's standards.

US Army — Rifleman

2011 - 2013

Received a rapid promotion to Specialist in 2012 due to hard work

SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript jQuery, RESTful APIs, Bootstrap 4, Firebase

Military Achievements & Training

Army Achievement Medal

Army Commendation Medal

Good Conduct Medal

U.S. Customs Border Clearance Agent Course

C - IED Level 3 Train the Trainer

Combative Trainer Course
Level 1

Combat Life Saver Course

Promoted from Specialist to Sergeant in 2014 due to outstanding leadership and professionalism.